# Resume

# Joong San Jun (Jayden)

#### **Personal Details**

Date of Birth: 23 August 1993

Address: 6 Wivenhoe Pl, Runcorn QLD 4113

Telephone: 0433 909 448

Email: pepejun123@hotmail.com

#### **Career Goal**

My career goal is to form my personal thoughts and behaviour in a way which will assist me to be flexible in any conditions. Also I am very friendly and interactive person which will provide positive outcomes within the relationship between co-workers. Due to several experiences within the customer service area, I can provide the high quality services to the customers and can solve the conflict between customers as well as customers need.

### **Employment History**

2009 - 2012 **Kentucky Fried Chicken (KFC)** (Sales Assistance and Staff). Kedron North next to Hungry Jacks, moved to Market Place at 2012 due to moving to different suburb.

2013 – 2014 Noggi (Frozen Yogurt Shop). CBD Myer Centre First Floor Opposite To Starbucks.

2016 – Current **LikeLion (Voluntary Work)** (Teaching Staff). Lesson is held at city library located near Brisbane City Council Building.

## Education

2004-2006

2014-2017	Queensland University of Technology (Bachelor of Information Technology) (Graduated)
2007-2011	Kelvin Grove State School (Australia)

Mairangi Bay Middle School (Auckland, New Zealand)

#### Qualifications:

Accomplished Korean & English Speaker.

Full First Aid Certified (20-May-2017). Certificate ID: 4144647-2640512

- HLTAID001 Provide Cardio Pulmonary Resuscitation (Completed)
- HLTAID002 Provide Basic Emergency Life Support (Completed)
- HLTAID003 Provide First Aid (Completed)

Queensland Certificate of Education (2011) OP9

#### **Skills**

- -Professional attitude punctuality and formality.
- -Accomplished Computer User (Microsoft Word/Excel/Powerpoint & others).
- -Ability to follow instructions and learn quickly.
- -Ability to communicate with other people
- -Ability to use few computer languages (C#, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Ruby on Rails)

#### Referee

Justin Kim

Head of Teaching Staff/Manager within Brisbane region, LikeLion

Mobile Phone: 0416 554 634

Email: justin@likelion.org

Harry Jeong

Teaching Staff, LikeLion

Mobile Phone: 0433 652 454

Email: hyun@likelion.org